

CONTACT DETAILS

Phone: +48 690 994 018

E-mail: tomazlis01@gmail.com LinkedIn: tomasz-lis-67b879261 Website: tommy-portfolio.dev GitHub: github.com/13-TOMMY

SKILLS

- Native speaker (C2) English language
- JavaScript, TypeScript, and React
- HTML5 and CSS (Tailwind, SASS/SCSS)
- Version control Git
- Figma, Photoshop, Firebase
- Node.js, Next.js, PostgreSQL (currently learning)
- Creating responsive projects and following a mobile-first approach.
- Applying coding standards and best practices
- Web performance optimisation
- Understanding of web accessibility (WCAG)

INTRESTS

- Programming
- Web development
- Computer assembly and repair
- Keeping up with the latest technology trends
- Hiking
- Reading biography books

TOMASZ LIS

I am a graduate of a 7-month front-end development bootcamp with a certificate confirming my skills and practical experience working on 8 different projects.

Currently, I am participating in a back-end development bootcamp. I have programming experience, mainly in JavaScript and React. Additionally, I am fluent in English, which I acquired during my 18-year stay in London. I am seeking a challenging job that will allow me to leverage my skills and experience.

EDUKACJA

ROOKS HEATH SIXTH FORM

·2017 - 2019

Business Studies (BETEC Level 3) - A/A Media Studies (A level) - C

FRONT-END BOOTCAMP AT MIMO

•February 2023 - September 2023 Font-end developer (JavaScript, React, CSS, HTML, Figma, Firebase)

DOŚWIADCZENIE

LEGACY PROPERTY CONSULTANTS -WSPARCIE TECHNICZNE - LONDYN

09/2019 - 02/2020

- Hardware monitoring and optimisation, fault reporting
- Configuration and troubleshooting of networks and mobile devices
- General hardware and network support for the company

FOX PLASTERING - LONDYN

- Client negotiations and communication
- Payment and invoice handling
- Transportation coordination and scheduling

EXPRESSO - SPEDYTOR - TARNÓW

09/2020 - 01/2021

- Contracting and communication with both foreign and domestic partners
- Coordinating land cargo transportation
- Document preparation and transport process oversight

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych dla potrzeb niezbędnych do realizacji procesu rekrutacji zgodnie z Rozporządzeniem Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) 2016/679 z dnia 27 kwietnia 2016 r. w sprawie ochrony osób fizycznych w związku z przetwarzaniem danych osobowych i w sprawie swobodnego przepływu takich danych oraz uchylenia dyrektywy 95/46/WE (RODO).